wellfinger.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy for Well Finger

## Privacy Policy for www.wellfinger.com 

* * *

At www.wellfinger.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.wellfinger.com and how it is used.

#### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.wellfinger.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

www.wellfinger.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.wellfinger.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.wellfinger.com and other sites on the Internet. 

#### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

#### Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.weefinger.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

We has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

if you require any other policy don't hesitate to contact us. 

* * *
